Finding aid to Buildings records CA.MS.00104
Smith College Archives
- College Hall
  - -Photographs
    - -Exterior-With Other Buildings, undated (Box 201, Folder 3)
    - -Exterior (Box 201)
    - -Interior-General, 1889- (Box 201, Folder 4)
    - -Interior-General (Box 201)
    - -Interior-Alpha Reading Room, 1886-1890 (Box 201, Folder 5)
    - -Interior-Art Gallery
      [see Museum of Art]
    - -Interior-College Hall Reading Room, 1883-1901 (Box 201, Folder 6)
    - -Interior-Library
      [see Library, College Hall]
    - -Interior-Special Features, undated (Box 201, Folder 7)
    - -Carillon-General, 1919- (Box 201, Folder 8)
    - -Carillon-Keyboard, 1932-1979 (Box 201, Folder 9)
    - -Carillon-Miscellaneous, 1974-1986; undated (Box 201, Folder 10)
  - -Sketches and Drawings (Architectural and Artistic), 1870- (Box 201, Folder 11)
- Conway House (Box 201.1, Folder 1)
- Cushing House
  [see also Quadrangle]
  - -General, 1960-; undated (Box 201.1, Folder 1a)
  - -House Library
    [see Libraries-House-Cushing]
  - -Photographs-Exterior, 1922-; undated (Box 201.1, Folder 2)
  - -Photographs-Interior, 1922 (Box 201.1, Folder 3)
  - -Photographs-Groups, 1925-; undated (Box 201.1, Folder 4)
- Cutter House
  [see also Ziskind House]
  - -General, 1955-; undated (Box 201.1, Folder 5)
  - -Photographs-Exterior, 1957-; undated (Box 201.1, Folder 6)
  - -Photographs-Interior, 1960 (Box 201.1, Folder 7)
  - -Photographs-Groups, 1958- (Box 201.1, Folder 8)
  - -Photographs-Groundbreaking and Construction, 1956 (Box 201.1, Folder 9)
  - -Sketches and Drawings (Architectural and Artistic), 1955-1974 (Box 201.1, Folder 10)
- Dawes House (18 Henshaw Avenue and 8 Bedford Terrace)
  - -General, 1929- (Box 201.2, Folder 1)
  - -History-see below (Box 201.2)
  - -Photographs-Exterior, 1897- (Box 201.2, Folder 2)
  - -Photographs-Groups, 1913- (Box 201.2, Folder 3)
- Davis Student Center
  [see Box 22]
- Dean's House
  [see College Lane, #7]
- Dean's House (never built)
  [see Flat File Drawer 6 (Appendix H) for plans]
- Delta Sigma Invitation House, 1910-1958 (Box 201.2, Folder 4)
- Delta Sigma Invitation House-Photographs, 1897-1912; undated (Box 201.2, Folder 5)
- Dickinson House
  - -General, 1901-1944 (Box 201.2, Folder 6)
  - -Photographs-Exterior and Interior, 1894-1944 (Box 201.2, Folder 7)
  - -Photographs-Groups, 1897-1944 (Box 201.2, Folder 8)
  - -Photographs-Fire, 1944 (Box 201.2, Folder 9)
- Dawes House-Dawes House History, 1943 (Box 201.2)
- Dr. Davenport's House at 91 Elm
  [see Henshaw House]
- Davis Student Center
  - -General, 1953-; undated (Box 203, Folder 1)
  - -Brochures, 1950-1953; undated (Box 203, Folder 2)
  - -Director's Records (Box 203)
    - -Association of College Unions, 1952-1963; undated (Box 203, Folder 3)
    - -Board of Counselors of SC-Davis Center Committee, 1954-1958 (Box 203, Folder 4)
    - -Board of Counselors of SC-Residence and Reca. Ctte, 1962-1969 (Box 203, Folder 5)
    - -Event Information, undated (Box 203, Folder 6)
    - -Memoranda re. Events and Use of Space, 1956-1970; undated (Box 203, Folder 7)
    - -Purchase Orders, Requisitions, Repairs, & Contracts, 1962-1968; undated (Box 203, Folder 8)
    - -Reports, 1954-1968 (Box 203, Folder 9)
    - -Space Requests and Event Scheduling, 1967-1970; undated (Box 203, Folder 10)
    - -Student Employment and Scheduling, 1949-1968; undated (Box 203, Folder 11)
    - -Miscellaneous, 1956-1970; undated (Box 203, Folder 12)
  - -Director's Records-Correspondence
    - -General, 1950-1965 (Box 203, Folder 13)
    - -General, 1966-1970 (Box 203, Folder 14)
    - -General, undated (Box 203, Folder 15)
    - -Fischer, Anne Clark 1921, 1957 (Box 203, Folder 16)
    - -Higginbotham, Elizabeth Bell 1932, 1959-1962 (Box 203, Folder 17)
    - -Snow, Florence Homer 1904, 1955-1957 (Box 203, Folder 18)
    - -Stiness, Alice Mott 1919, 1957-1961 (Box 203, Folder 19)
    - -Waite, Lavinia Fyke 1925, 1956-1960 (Box 203, Folder 20)
  - -Floor Plans
    [see Flat File Drawer 6 (Appendix H) for floor plans as Faunce Hall]
  - -Loan Library
    [see Libraries-Loan Library]
  - -Photographs-Exterior, 1921-; undated (Box 203, Folder 21)
  - -Photographs-Interior, 1947-; undated (Box 203, Folder 22)
- Dewey House
  - -General, 1881-1994 (Box 204, Folder 1)
  - -Histories, 1922-1953 (Box 204, Folder 2)
  - -Artifacts
  - -Dewey Family, 1982; undated (Box 204, Folder 3)
  - -House Government
    - -General, 1967-1991 (Box 204, Folder 4)
    - -House President's Notebook, 1960-1982 (Box 204, Folder 5)
    - -Vice President's Notebook, 1963-1979 (Box 204, Folder 6)
    - -Minutes, 1989-1991 (Box 204, Folder 7)
  - -Residents List / Register / Roster, 1956-71; 1990-91 (Box 204, Folder 8)
  - -Photographs
    - -Exterior, 1877-1900 (Box 204, Folder 9)
    - -Exterior, 1901- (Box 204, Folder 10)
    - -Exterior, undated (Box 204.1, Folder 1)
    - -Exterior-Special Features, undated (Box 204.1, Folder 2)
    - -Exterior-With Other Buildings, 1878-1911 (Box 204.1, Folder 3)
    - -Exterior-With Other Buildings, undated (Box 204.1, Folder 4)
    - -Exterior (Box 204.1)
    - -Interior, 1890- (Box 204.1, Folder 5)
    - -Interior (Box 204.1)
    - -Groups, 1880-1949 (Box 204.1, Folder 6)
    - -Groups, 1950- (Box 204.1, Folder 7)
    - -Groups-Upperclasswomen, 1959 (Box 204.1, Folder 8)
    - -Groups (Box 204.1)
- Drew Hall
- Duckett House
  [see Eleanor Duckett House]
- Earle St. and West St., #182, 1995 (Box 205, Folder 1)
- Eleanor Duckett House, 1967- (Box 205, Folder 2)
  [see also Southwick House]
- Elizabeth Drew House / Hall, 1900- (Box 205, Folder 3)
- Elizabeth Mason Infirmary
  [see Infirmary-Elizabeth Mason]
- Ellen Emerson House
  - -General, undated (Box 205, Folder 4)
  - -Artifacts
  - -Guest Book, 1922-1944 (Box 205, Folder 5)
  - -Guest Book, 1944-1971 (Box 205, Folder 6)
  - -Medieval Banquet, undated (Box 205, Folder 7)
  - -Medieval Banquet-Clippings, 1937-1940 (Box 205, Folder 8)
  - -Class of 1937 Round Robin [3 rounds], Jan 1977-Dec 1981 (Box 205, Folder 9)
  - -Class of 1937 Round Robin [3 rounds], Jan 1982-Aug 1986 (Box 205, Folder 10)
  - -Class of 1937 Round Robin [3 rounds], Aug 1986-Feb 1989 (Box 205, Folder 11)
  - -Class of 1937 Round Robin [3 rounds], Feb 1989-Jul 1992 (Box 205, Folder 12)
  - -Class of 1937 Round Robin [3 rounds], Apr 1992-Oct 1995 (Box 205, Folder 13)
  - -Class of 1937 Round Robin [1 round], Nov 1995- (Box 205, Folder 14)
  - -Photographs
    - -Exterior, 1922- (Box 205.1, Folder 1)
    - -Interior, 1925 (Box 205.1, Folder 2)
    - -Groups, 1922- (Box 205.1, Folder 3)
    - -Medieval Banquet, 1910- (Box 205.1, Folder 4)
  - -Sketches and Drawings (Artistic), undated (Box 205.1, Folder 5)
- Elm Street Houses
  - -General, 1885-1935 (Box 205.1, Folder 6)
  - -#s 20, 26, 38, undated (Box 205.1, Folder 7)
    [see also Gateway House (# 20 Elm Street)]
  - -# 41
    [see Southwick House and see Eleanor Duckett House]
  - -# 50
    [see Clark House]
  - -# 70
  - -# 76, 1981 (Box 205.1, Folder 8)
  - -# 79 Henshaw Group, 1910-1956 (Box 205.1, Folder 9)
    [see also Henshaw House]
  - -# 84
  - -# 90 (Methodist Church), 1974 (Box 205.1, Folder 10)
  - -# 91
  - -# 96
    [see Haven House]
  - -# 105
    [see Sessions Annex]
  - -# 109
    [see Sessions House]
  - -# 112
    [see Hopkins House]
  - -# 116
    [see Park House Annex]
  - -# 133, undated (Box 205.1, Folder 11)
  - -#s 134, 136, 1982 (Box 205.1, Folder 12)
  - -# 150, 1928- (Box 205.1, Folder 13)
  - -# 150, 156, 164, 168-Photographs, 1921-1930 (Box 205.1, Folder 14)
  - -# 150, 156, 168-Registers / Rosters, 1922-1935 (Box 205.1, Folder 15)
  - -# 156
    [see Tenney House]
  - -# 240, 1909 (Box 205.1, Folder 16)
- Engineering Building, 2001 (Box 205.1, Folder 17)
- Even Inn
  [see Arnold Avenue #16]
- Faculty Club (College Lane, #51), 1941- (Box 206, Folder 1)
- Faculty Club-Renovations
- Faculty Clubhouse
  [see Faculty Club and see Prospect Street, # 10]
- Faunce Hall
- Faunce House
  [see Parsons House]
- Faunce House Annex
  [see Parsons House Annex]
- Feather
- Field House, 1938- (Box 206, Folder 2)
- Fine Arts Center
  [see Museum of Art-Fine Arts Center]
- Fort Hill Faculty Apartments, 1961-1972 (Box 206, Folder 3)
- Fort Hill (Graduate) House
  - -General, 1956-96; undated (Box 206, Folder 4)
  - -Correspondence with Elizabeth Young, House Mother, 1950-1960 (Box 206, Folder 5)
  - -Scrapbook, 1946-1947 (Box 206, Folder 6)
  - -Scrapbook, 1947-1948 (Box 206, Folder 7)
  - -Scrapbook, 1948-1949 (Box 206, Folder 8)
  - -Scrapbook, 1949-1950 (Box 207, Folder 1)
  - -Scrapbook, 1950-51; 1951-52 (Box 207, Folder 2)
  - -Scrapbook, 1952-1955 (Box 207, Folder 3)
  - -Photographs, 1893-1957 (Box 207, Folder 4)
- Franklin King House
  - -General, 1936-; undated (Box 207, Folder 5)
  - -Murals, 1979 (Box 207, Folder 6)
  - -Photographs-Exterior and Interior, 1936-; undated (Box 207, Folder 7)
  - -Photographs-Groups, 1942-; undated (Box 207, Folder 8)
- Franklin King Residences
  [see College Lane, #7 and College Lane, # 51]
- French House
  [see Dawes House, West Street # 75, and Bedford Terrace # 8]
- Friedman Apartments, 1975- (Box 207, Folder 9)
- Gardiner House
  - -General, 1906-; undated (Box 208, Folder 1)
  - -Bookplate
    [see Libraries-Bookplates-House Libraries]
  - -Financial Records, 1951-1953 (Box 208, Folder 2)
  - -History, 1926-1951 (Box 208, Folder 3)
  - -History, 1952-1953 (Box 208, Folder 4)
  - -History, 1954-1955 (Box 208, Folder 5)
  - -History, 1956-1958 (Box 208, Folder 6)
  - -Knitters, 1948 (Box 208, Folder 7)
  - -Scrapbook, 1999-2000 (Box 208, Folder 8)
  - -Photographs
    - -Exterior and Interior, 1926- (Box 208, Folder 9)
    - -Groups, 1933-; undated (Box 208, Folder 10)
    - -Groups-History Album, 1927-1942 (Box 208, Folder 11)
    - -Groups (Box 208)
  - -Scrapbook, 2004-2005 (Box 208)
  - -Scrapbook, 1926-1945
    [see Oversize Box 6 (Appendix H)]
- Garrison Hall, 1956- (Box 209, Folder 1)
- Gateway House
  - -General, undated (Box 209, Folder 2)
  - -Guest Book, 1924-1938 (Box 209, Folder 3)
  - -Photographs, 1880-1889 (Box 209, Folder 4)
  - -Photographs, 1890-1899 (Box 209, Folder 5)
  - -Photographs, 1900- (Box 209, Folder 6)
  - -Photographs, undated (Box 209, Folder 7)
- Geology Building (never built), undated (Box 209, Folder 8)
- German House (8 Bedford Terrace)
  - -General, 1935-1956; undated (Box 209, Folder 9)
  - -Correspondence, 1938-1946; undated (Box 209, Folder 10)
  - -Dramatics, 1955-1956 (Box 209, Folder 11)
  - -Eppendorff, Lina, 1935-1940 (Box 209, Folder 12)
  - -House President's Notebook, 1953-1954 (Box 209.1, Folder 1)
  - -House President's Notebook, 1955-1957 (Box 209.1, Folder 2)
  - -Signs, undated (Box 209.1, Folder 3)
  - -Photographs, 1939-1957 (Box 209.1, Folder 4)
- Gill Hall, 1917-1977 (Box 209.1, Folder 5)
  [see also Campus School]
- Gillett House
  [see also Northrop House]
  - -General, 1919- (Box 209.1, Folder 6)
  - -Artifacts
  - -Floor Plan, undated
    [see Oversize Box 4 (Appendix H)]
  - -House President's Notebook, 1970s (Box 209.1, Folder 7)
  - -Photographs-Exterior, 1910- (Box 209.1, Folder 8)
  - -Photographs-Groups, 1912-; undated (Box 209.1, Folder 9)
  - -Photographs-Groups, 1966
- Graduate House
  [see Elizabeth Drew House, Fort Hill Graduate House, Bedford Terrace #8, Belmont Avenue #30]
- Graham Hall
  [see Museum of Art-Fine Arts Center--Graham Hall]
- Green Street
  - -General, 1989-1996 (Box 209.2, Folder 1)
  - -# 10
    [see Snowe House]
  - -#s 12, 14, 1895 (Box 209.2, Folder 2)
  - -# 20
    [see 10. Postcard File]
  - -# 26, 1913-1920 (Box 209.2, Folder 3)
  - -# 30 (Lapan Inn), 1914-1960 (Box 209.2, Folder 4)
  - -# 30-Photographs-Exterior and Interior, 1916-1960 (Box 209.2, Folder 5)
  - -# 30-Photographs-Groups, 1905-1927 (Box 209.2, Folder 6)
  - -#s 36, 39, 1925 (Box 209.2, Folder 7)
  - -#s 44, 54, 1988-1993 (Box 209.2, Folder 8)
  - -#s 78-86, 1992 (Box 209.2, Folder 9)
- Gymnasium
  - -General, 1925- (Box 210, Folder 1)
  - -General-Floor plans and elevation drawings
  - -Ainsworth Gym
    - -General, 1977- (Box 210, Folder 2)
    - -Architectural Plans
    - -Formal Opening
      - -General, 1977 (Box 210, Folder 3)
      - -Correspondence-General-Acceptances, 1977 (Box 210, Folder 4)
      - -Correspondence-General-Regrets, 1977 (Box 210, Folder 5)
      - -Correspondence-Ainsworth Family, 1977 (Box 210, Folder 6)
      - -Correspondence-Special Invitees, 1977 (Box 210, Folder 7)
    - -Planning and Financing of, 1968-1976 (Box 210, Folder 8)
      [see also Gymnasium-Scott]
    - -Photographs
      - -Exterior, 1976- (Box 210, Folder 9)
      - -Interior, 1977- (Box 210, Folder 10)
      - -Formal Opening, 1977 (Box 210, Folder 11)
    - -Sketches and Drawings (Architectural), undated (Box 210, Folder 12)
  - -Alumnae Gym
    - -General, 1889- (Box 210.1, Folder 1)
    - -Architectural Plans
      [see Flat File Drawer 6 (Appendix H) for original plans and renovations]
    - -Artifacts
    - -Dedication, 1983 (Box 210.1, Folder 2)
    - -Gymnasium Committee, 1887-1891 (Box 210.1, Folder 3)
    - -Plaques, undated (Box 210.1, Folder 4)
    - -Preservation and Conversion, 1975-1981; 2001 (Box 210.1, Folder 5)
      [see also Flat File Drawer 6 (Appendix H) for Save Alumnae Gym poster]
    - -Photographs
      - -Exterior-East View, 1985-1917; 1985 (Box 210.1, Folder 6)
      - -Exterior-Northeast View, 1897-1982; undated (Box 210.1, Folder 7)
      - -Exterior-South View, 1897-1904; 1994 (Box 210.1, Folder 8)
      - -Exterior-Southeast View, 1894-1917; 1981 (Box 210.1, Folder 9)
      - -Exterior-West / Northwest View, 1891-1983 (Box 210.1, Folder 10)
      - -Interior, 1894- 1930; undated (Box 210.1, Folder 11)
      - -Interior-CA / SSC, 1983- (Box 210.1, Folder 12)
      - -Special Features, 1976-1988; undated (Box 210.1, Folder 13)
    - -Sketches and Drawings (Artistic), 1894 (Box 210.1, Folder 14)
  - -Equestrian Center, 1975- (Box 211, Folder 1)
  - -First
    [see Gymnasium-Old]
  - -Indoor Track and Tennis Facility, 1983- (Box 211, Folder 2)
  - -Old
    - -General, 1979-1934; undated (Box 211, Folder 3)
    - -Photographs-Exterior (Lilly Hall location), 1876-1886 (Box 211, Folder 4)
    - -Photographs-Exterior (Neilson Library location), 1886-1909 (Box 211, Folder 5)
    - -Photographs-Interior, 1879-1891 (Box 211, Folder 6)
  - -Scott
    - -General, 1924- (Box 211, Folder 7)
    - -Architectural Plans
    - -Bookplate
    - -Photographs-Exterior, 1924- (Box 211, Folder 8)
    - -Photographs-Interior, 1925- (Box 211, Folder 9)
    - -Sketches and Drawings (Architectural), undated (Box 211, Folder 10)
- Hampshire House
  - -General, 1951-1989 (Box 212, Folder 1)
  - -History, 1938-1969 (Box 212, Folder 2)
  - -Constitution, 1945-1990 (Box 212, Folder 3)
  - -House Government, 1955-1989 (Box 212, Folder 4)
  - -Renovations
  - -Photographs-Exterior, 1975-1990 (Box 212, Folder 5)
  - -Photographs-Groups, 1945-1995; undated (Box 212, Folder 6)
  - -Photographs-as Sophie's Terrace Cafe, 1980-1987 (Box 212, Folder 7)
- Mrs. Hatch's House
  [see West Street # 75]
- Hatfield House / Hall
  - -General, 1922-; undated (Box 212, Folder 8)
  - -History, 1920-1927 (Box 212, Folder 9)
  - -Finances, 1923-1925 (Box 212, Folder 10)
  - -Guest Book, 1894-1924 (Box 212, Folder 11)
  - -House Library
    [see Libraries-House-Hatfield]
  - -Photographs
    - -Exterior, 1877-1920 (Box 212, Folder 12)
    - -Exterior, 1921- (Box 212, Folder 13)
    - -Exterior, undated (Box 212, Folder 14)
    - -Exterior-With Other Buildings, 1877-1928; undated (Box 213, Folder 1)
    - -Exterior (Box 213)
      [see also Oversize Box 5 (Appendix H)]
    - -Interior, 1881; undated (Box 213, Folder 2)
    - -Groups, 1888-1926 (Box 213, Folder 3)
- Haven House
  - -General, 1902-; undated (Box 213, Folder 4)
  - -History 1913-1956-Foreword, 1912 (Box 213, Folder 5)
  - -History 1913-1956-House Photograph Page, 1907 (Box 213, Folder 6)
  - -History 1913-1956, 1913-1914 (Box 213, Folder 7)
  - -History 1913-1956, 1914-1915 (Box 213, Folder 8)
  - -History 1913-1956, 1915-1916 (Box 213, Folder 9)
  - -History 1913-1956, 1916-1917 (Box 213, Folder 10)
  - -History 1913-1956, 1917-1918 (Box 213, Folder 11)
  - -History 1913-1956, 1918-1919 (Box 213, Folder 12)
  - -History 1913-1956, 1919-1920 (Box 213, Folder 13)
  - -History 1913-1956, 1920-1921 (Box 213, Folder 14)
  - -History 1913-1956, 1921-1922 (Box 213, Folder 15)
  - -History 1913-1956, 1922-1923 (Box 213, Folder 16)
  - -History 1913-1956, 1923-1924 (Box 213, Folder 17)
  - -History 1913-1956, 1924-1925 (Box 213, Folder 18)
  - -History 1913-1956, 1925-1926 (Box 213, Folder 19)
  - -History 1913-1956, 1926-1927 (Box 213, Folder 20)
  - -History 1913-1956, 1928-1929 (Box 213, Folder 21)
  - -History 1913-1956, 1929-1930 (Box 213, Folder 22)
  - -History 1913-1956, 1930-1931 (Box 213, Folder 23)
  - -History 1913-1956, 1931-1932 (Box 213, Folder 24)
  - -History 1913-1956, 1932-1933 (Box 213, Folder 25)
  - -History 1913-1956, 1933-1934 (Box 213, Folder 26)
  - -History 1913-1956, 1934-1935 (Box 213, Folder 27)
  - -History 1913-1956, 1935-1936 (Box 213.1, Folder 1)
  - -History 1913-1956, 1936-1937 (Box 213.1, Folder 2)
  - -History 1913-1956, 1937-1938 (Box 213.1, Folder 3)
  - -History 1913-1956, 1940-1941 (Box 213.1, Folder 4)
  - -History 1913-1956, 1942-1943 (Box 213.1, Folder 5)
  - -History 1913-1956, 1947-1948 (Box 213.1, Folder 6)
  - -History 1913-1956, 1955-1956 (Box 213.1, Folder 7)
  - -History 1913-1956, undated (Box 213.1, Folder 8)
  - -Artifacts
    [see Appendix E]-Haven House Hash
  - -Photographs
    - -Exterior, 1904- (Box 213.1, Folder 9)
    - -Interior, 1904- (Box 213.1, Folder 10)
    - -Groups, 1901-1931 (Box 213.1, Folder 11)
    - -Groups, 1932- (Box 213.1, Folder 12)
    - -Groups-Photo Albums, 1954; '56; '60 (Box 213.1, Folder 13)
  - -Sketches and Drawings (Artistic), 1979 (Box 213.1, Folder 14)
  - -House map, spring dance tickets, misc (Box 213.1, Folder 14a)
  - -Photographs, 1950, 1953 (Box 213.1, Folder 15)
  - -Scrapbook on Haven / Wesley Greek foster child, 1952-1957
- Henshaw Avenue
  - -Henshaw Group, House History, 1924-1953 (Box 214, Folder 1a)
  - -General and House Registers / Rosters, 1923-1950 (Box 214, Folder 1)
  - -# 10, 1912-1931 (Box 214, Folder 2)
  - -# 11, 1890-1954 (Box 214, Folder 3)
  - -# 14, 1890 (Box 214, Folder 4)
  - -# 17, undated (Box 214, Folder 5)
  - -# 18
    [see Dawes House]
  - -# 20
  - -# 25
    [see Hover House and see Parsons House Annex]
  - -Henshaw House
    - -General, undated (Box 214, Folder 6)
    - -Artifacts
    - -Photographs, 1918-1952; undated (Box 214, Folder 7)
- Hillyer Art Gallery
  [see Museum of Art-Fine Arts Center-Hillyer Hall and see Libraries-Hillyer Art Library]
- Hopkins Houses
  - -General, 1881- (Box 214, Folder 8)
  - -Facebook, c.1997 (Box 214, Folder 8a)
  - -Notes, c.1997 (Box 214, Folder 8b)
  - -Elf Books, 1980's (Box 214, Folder 8c)
  - -Forever Friends - poster
  - -Photographs
    - -Exterior-Hopkins Group, 1919-1999 (Box 214, Folder 9)
    - -Exterior-Hopkins House, 1942-1994 (Box 214, Folder 10)
    - -Exterior-Hopkins A, 1981 (Box 214, Folder 11)
    - -Exterior-Hopkins B, 1983; undated (Box 214, Folder 12)
    - -Groups, 1896-1994; undated (Box 214, Folder 13)
  - -Scrapbook, 1951-1955
- Hopkins House - Hover House (Box 214.1)
- Hover House, 1967-1984 (Box 214, Folder 14)
  [see also Parsons House Annex]
- Hover House-Journal, 1984 (Box 214, Folder 15)
- Hubbard House
  - -General, 1882- (Box 215, Folder 1)
  - -History, 1922-1941 (Box 215, Folder 2)
  - -History, 1966-1970 (Box 215, Folder 3)
  - -Anniversary, 50th and 60th, 1929; 1939 (Box 215, Folder 4)
  - -Anniversary, 90th, 1969 (Box 215, Folder 5)
  - -Anniversary, 100th
    - -General, 1978 (Box 215, Folder 6)
    - -Correspondence-General, 1978 (Box 215, Folder 7)
    - -Correspondence-Acceptances, 1978 (Box 215, Folder 8)
    - -Correspondence-Congratulations, 1978 (Box 215, Folder 9)
    - -Correspondence-Regrets, 1978 (Box 215, Folder 10)
    - -Correspondence-Thank-You Notes, 1978 (Box 215, Folder 11)
  - -Artifacts
  - -House President's Notebook, 1970-1979 (Box 215, Folder 12)
  - -Roster / Register, 1922-1968; 1992 (Box 215, Folder 13)
  - -Tertium Quid, 1897 (Box 215, Folder 14)
  - -Vacation Register, 1976 (Box 215, Folder 15)
  - -Photographs
    - -Exterior, 1880-1915; undated (Box 216, Folder 1)
    - -Exterior, 1916-; undated (Box 216, Folder 2)
    - -Exterior-With Other Buildings, 1883-1895 (Box 216, Folder 3)
    - -Interior-Common Areas, 1889; undated (Box 216, Folder 4)
    - -Interior-Student Rooms, 1882-1901 (Box 216, Folder 5)
    - -Groups, 1879-1907 (Box 216, Folder 6)
    - -Groups (Box 216)
    - -Groups, 1921- (Box 216, Folder 7)
    - -Groups-Photo Album, 1958-1959 (Box 216, Folder 8)
    - -Groups-Photo Album, 1940-1954
      [see Oversize Box 5 (Appendix H)]
  - -Scrapbooks
    - -Senior Scrapbook, 1960
      [see Box 42]
    - -Scrapbook, 1991-1992
      [see Oversize Box 8 (Appendix H)]
    - -Scrapbook, 1992-1993
      [see Oversize Box 7 (Appendix H)]
- Hubbard House-Senior Scrapbook: To Mother Hubbard From Her Seniors, 1960 (Box 216.1)
- Infirmary-First, 1905 (Box 217, Folder 1)
- Infirmary-Elizabeth Mason Infirmary
  - -General, undated (Box 217, Folder 2)
  - -History, 1916-1919 (Box 217, Folder 3)
  - -History, 1941-1942 (Box 217, Folder 4)
  - -History, 1954- (Box 217, Folder 5)
  - -50th Anniversary
    - -General, 1969 (Box 217, Folder 6)
    - -Correspondence-Acceptances, 1969 (Box 217, Folder 7)
    - -Correspondence-Regrets, 1969 (Box 217, Folder 8)
    - -Invitation Lists and Seating Plans, 1969 (Box 217, Folder 9)
  - -Health Services
    - -Brochures, 1965-1980; undated (Box 217, Folder 10)
    - -Brochures, 1981- (Box 217, Folder 11)
    - -Counseling Services, 1987 (Box 217, Folder 12)
    - -Forms, 1973- (Box 217, Folder 13)
    - -Insurance, 1971- (Box 217, Folder 14)
    - -Miscellaneous, 1967- (Box 217, Folder 15)
  - -Photographs
    - -Exterior, 1919- (Box 217, Folder 16)
    - -Exterior-Florence Gilman Pavilion, 1944-1954; undated (Box 217, Folder 17)
    - -Exterior-FGP-Groundbreaking / Construction, 1942-1943 (Box 217, Folder 18)
    - -Exterior-FGP-Third Floor Addition, 1951-1953 (Box 217, Folder 19)
    - -Exterior-WAVES Temporary Building, 1942-1943 (Box 217, Folder 20)
    - -Exterior-Special Features, 1965; undated (Box 217, Folder 21)
    - -Interior, 1941- (Box 217, Folder 22)
  - -Sketches and Drawings (Architectural and Artistic), 1940
    [see Oversize Box 5 and Flat File Drawer 6 (Appendix H)]
- John M. Greene Hall
  - -General, 1901-1911 (Box 218, Folder 1)
  - -General, 1938-2001 (Box 218, Folder 2)
  - -History-Baker Properties and Copeland Residence, 1977 (Box 218, Folder 3)
  - -Architectural Plans
    [see Flat File Drawer 7 (Appendix H)]
  - -Artifacts
  - -Gates Project
  - -Organ, 1910-1998; undated (Box 218, Folder 4)
  - -Photographs
    - -Construction, 1909-1910 (Box 218, Folder 5)
    - -Exterior-East View, 1910-94 (Box 218, Folder 6)
    - -Exterior-East View-Northeast Angle, 1910-1920 (Box 218, Folder 7)
    - -Exterior-East View -Southeast Angle, 1910-1982; undated (Box 218, Folder 8)
    - -Exterior-East View -South Angle, 1910-1953 (Box 218, Folder 9)
    - -Exterior-North View, 1935 (Box 218, Folder 10)
    - -Exterior-Southeast View, 1910-1920 (Box 218, Folder 11)
    - -Exterior-South View, 1915 (Box 218, Folder 12)
    - -Exterior-West and Southwest Views, 1915-1927 (Box 218, Folder 13)
    - -Exterior-Special Features, 1981-1993 (Box 218, Folder 14)
    - -Exterior-Special Features-Steps, 1950-1990 (Box 218, Folder 15)
    - -Interior, 1910-1946; undated (Box 218, Folder 16)
    - -Interior, 1947-79 (Box 218, Folder 17)
    - -Interior-Reconstruction, 1946-1947 (Box 218, Folder 18)
  - -Flags (Box 218.1)
- Jordan House
  - -General, 1955-1998; undated (Box 218, Folder 19)